PATRICK RAMOS



PROFILE

Has experience in creating a Shopping Cart website, and a Student Info System using Visual Studio as an IDE. Is a novice baker that can prepare small variety of breads with reliable speed and efficiency. A detail-oriented individual with strong analytical skills. Highly reliable and a team player to provide quality service and product to customers.

Birthdate 12/13/94 Height 163 cm Weight 53 kg

SKILLS

- SQL Server
- C# Programming Language
- Microsoft Office
- Licensed Non-Pro Driver
- Baking

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION -MAJOR IN COMPUTER APPLICATIONS

De La Salle - College of Saint Benilde 2010 - 2015

EXPERIENCE

FARMER/STORE OWNER

Farmland and Convenience Store (Family Owned)

Nov 2015 - Oct 2019

- Responsible for buying crops to till farm land
- · Deciding when to till land
- Selling produce to buyers
- Manages store
- · Inventory checking, refilling

SALES ASSOCIATE

SM Pampanga

Oct 2019 - March 2020

- Provides customer service
- Keeping store organized and clean, and doing inventory
- Works under varying schedules, and attends store meetings

FARMER/STORE OWNER

Farmland and Convenience Store (Family Owned)

Mar 2020 - Sep 2023

- Responsible for buying crops to till farm land
- · Deciding when to till land
- Selling produce to buyers
- Manages store
- · Inventory checking, refilling
- Baking salted bread to display every morning

SERVICE CREW

Burger King SM Pampanga

Sep 2023 - Present

- Creating burgers and special customer orders
- Keeping store organized and clean
- Works under varying schedules



1 09355405697



ptrck.rms.13@gmail.com



2 Purok6b, 603, Lanang, Candaba, Pampanga